(Leonard:)What, you actually
want to meet her?
(Penny:)No, but now that you're
being weird about it,
(Penny:)maybe I should.
(Leonard:)I'm not being weird.
(Leonard:)Am I being weird?
(Sheldon:)Yes.
(Sheldon:)And that's coming from me.
(Leonard:)Fine, you want to meet her?
(Penny:)No, I just want to know
that when you're at work,
(Penny:)there's nothing going on.
(Leonard:)How many times
do I have to tell you?
(Leonard:)I have no interest
in this woman.
(Penny:)Yeah, well, maybe she
has interest in you.
(Sheldon:)In Leonard?
(Sheldon:)Oh, even the Sparkletts guy
could see that's unlikely.
(Penny:)I guess my big problem is
I never saw Leonard
(Penny:)as the kind of guy who would
do something like this.
(Amy:)Anybody can make a mistake
in a weak moment.
(sighs)
What do you think?
Oh, I don't know what to think.
(Bernadette:)But then again,
I just found out about it.
(Penny:)You know, I fell in love
with Leonard
(Penny:)because he wasn't
anything like the guys
(Penny:)I was used to dating.
(Penny:)I mean, I knew those guys
weren't above cheating
(Penny:)because that's usually
how we met.
(Amy:)Come on, you know
Leonard's not like that.